I'm Matt Clark. I'm the c e o and co-founder of amazing.com,
and a co-owner of a coffee company called Life Boost Coffee.
I found out about Jack through a investor that I followed in a Monish pry.
Uh, I've been very successful,
done a lot of things with Warren Buffett and his business partner,
Charlie Munger, and that's how I found out about Jack and the roadmap process.
And for me, you know,
I'd been building businesses and stuff for over 10 years and had had some
success, had had a lot of challenges, and kind of,
it came to a point where I felt like something was missing.
Like I knew some stuff that I was good at and knew some stuff that I was not
good at,
but was having a hard time really pinpointing like where I should spend my time.
And so Monish spoke very highly of Jack in the roadmap process that he went
through 25 years ago or so. And so I, I thought it'd be a good deal for me.
So I contacted Jack, he was willing to work with me and, uh,
so we worked together,
got got to work on the roadmap process and I found it fascinating, you know,
especially with the 360 interviews, um, interviewing friends and family members.
And then after that,
kind of triangulating that with his own conversations with me,
we did six calls or so. And then also, um,
his own background as a psychologist and the assessments that I did and sort of
gave me a lot of clarity and stuff I didn't expect in terms of like,
what really drives me and what's likely gonna light me up and gimme the best
results, um, personal fulfillment wise and probably also success wise.
And so this, this process was unlike anything else. I'd read a bunch of books,
done different surveys and stuff like that,
but nothing really compared to having an expert like Jack who'd been doing this
for so long to do this one-on-one with me.
And so I found the process invaluable.
And so if you're somebody who really wants to figure out how to get the most out
of your life, out of your day, out of your work pursuit,
I highly recommend working with Jack.